Oh, look, look! There's Joey's picture!
快看这上面有乔伊
This is so exciting!
还有点小激动呢
You can always spot someone who's never seen his plays before.
这显然是没看过乔伊的表演啊
Notice, no fear. No sense of impending doom.
没有恐惧 对迫近的厄运毫无感觉
The exclamation point in the title scares me.
标题上的感叹号吓到我了
It's not just Freud, it's Freud!
显得这么有爆发力
Magic is about to happen!
见证奇迹的时刻到了
Well, Eva...
伊娃
...we've done some excellent work here.
我们做了不少工作了
And I would have to say...
要我说的话
...your problem is quite clear.
你的问题已经显而易见了
All you want is a dinkle
(歌词太黄 已不忍直视)
What you envy's a schwang
A thing through which you can tinkle
(有兴趣请自行百度)
To play with or simply let hang
老·友·记
S01E05  The One With the Butt
第一季第六集  疯狂的屁股
■
字幕制作
Subtitled By
@张纳德nerd
■
讨论邮箱
Discuss
f6dicuss@163.com (或私信)
■
鸣谢
Special Thanks
Psychd(英文字幕)
I feel violated.
我感觉被侵犯了
Did anybody else feel like peeling their skin off...
为了转移注意力 我都恨不得
...to have something else to do?
撕破皮肤了
Ross, 10:00.
罗斯 十点钟
Is it? It feels like 2.
才十点 我感觉都凌晨了
No, 10:00!
不是 十点钟
What?
啥
There's a beautiful woman at 8, 9, 10:00!
有个美女 处于八 九 十点钟方向
Hello!
不错啊
She's amazing!
太完美了
She makes the women I dream about look like short, fat, bald men.
和她一比 我的梦中情人简直就是矮丑挫啊
Go over to her. She's not with anyone.
去搭讪啊 她自己来的
And what would my opening line be?
那我应该怎么开头好呢
Excuse me...
不好意思...
Come on, she's a person. You can do it.
不就是个女的嘛 你能行的
Could she be more out of my league? Ross, back me up.
完全不在我的能力范围 罗斯 帮帮我
He could never get a woman like that in a million years.
找这种妹子 钱德还早了一百万年
But you always see these beautiful women with these "nothing" guys.
但是美女身边通常都是屌丝
You could be one of those guys.
所以你还是有希望的
-You could do that.  -You think?
-没问题的  -你们确定
Absolutely!
当然了
I can't believe I'm even considering this.
真不相信我会这么干
-I'm very aware of my tongue. -Come on.
-我一向言行谨慎啊  -快去吧
Here goes.
走你
Yes?
怎么了
Hi
嗨
Okay, next word would be...
接下来应该说...
...uh, Chandler.
钱德
Chandler is my name and, uh...
我叫钱德 然后...
Hi!
嗨
Yes, you said that.
你说过'嗨'了
Yes! Yes, I did. But what I didn't say...
没错 我没说过的是
What I wanted to say was, uh...
我真正想说的是...
...would you like to go out with me? Thank you. Good night.
我能约你出去吗 谢谢 晚安
Chandler?
钱德
There he is!
明星出来啦
-I didn't know you could dance!  -You were in a play!
-我都不知道你会跳舞啊  -你是主角啊
What'd you think?
你们觉得怎么样
-I didn't know you could dance!  -You were in a play!
-我都不知道你会跳舞啊  -你是主角啊
Come on, it wasn't that bad. I was the lead.
拜托 没这么烂吧 我可是领唱
It was better than the troll thing. At least you got to see my head.
这比轮唱好多了 至少可以看到我的脑袋吧
-You're right.  -We saw your head.
-没错  -确实看见你脑袋了
She said yes! She said yes!
她同意了 同意啦
Awful play, man! Whoa!
演的烂死了 靠
Her name's Aurora. She's Italian and she pronounces my name "Chandler."
她叫奥萝拉 意大利人 念我名字都念得这么性感
I like that better. The usher gave me this to give to you.
这么念挺不错 对了 招待让我把这个给你
-What is it?  -The Estelle Leonard Talent Agency.
-啥啊  -艾斯黛尔经纪公司
An agency left me its card. Maybe they wanna sign me!
有经纪人给我留名片啦 没准是想签我
Based on this play?
就因为这个表演
Based on this play!
完全是因为这次表演嘛
Hey, kids!
嘿 小鬼们
Hey, Chandler.
嘿 钱德
No, because this line is passion, and this is just a line.
这条才是感情线 这条啥都不是
I've been here seven seconds, and you haven't asked me how my date went.
我都坐这7秒钟了 没人问我约会的咋样吗
How was your date, Chandler?
约会怎么样啊 钱德
It was unbelievable!
极端犀利啊
I've never met anyone like her. She's had the most amazing life!
我从来没见过生活这么精彩的人
She was in the Israeli army.
她曾经在以色列参军
None of the bullets hit the engine block...
还好没有子弹打中引擎
...so we made it to the border.
于是我们到了边境
But just barely and I...
但是挺危险 然后我...
I've been talking about myself all night long. I'm sorry.
我整晚都在说我自己 真不好意思
What about you? Tell me your stories.
给我讲讲你的故事吧
All right, once...
好吧 有一次
...once I got on the subway, right?
有一次我坐地铁
And it was at night...
在晚上坐的
...and I rode it all the way to Brooklyn...
然后一直坐到了布鲁克林
...just for the hell of it.
纯属是闲的
We talked till 2. It was this perfect evening.
我们一直聊到两点 完美的夜晚
More or less.
其实也不太完美
Suddenly, we realized we were in Yemen.
突然 我们意识到那里是也门
I'm sorry, so "we" is?
不好意思 我们都是谁呀
"We" is me and Rick.
是我和瑞克
-Who's Rick? -Who's Rick?
-瑞克是谁  -瑞克是哪位
My husband.
我丈夫
-Oh, so you're divorced?  -No.
-你离婚了  -没有啊
I'm sorry. So you're widowed?
抱歉 那你丈夫去世了
Hopefully?
希望是
No, I'm still married.
没有 我们还是夫妻
So how would your husband feel about you sitting here with me...
那我挺好奇你丈夫的想法 你和我约会
...sliding your foot so far up my leg...
把你的脚伸到我腿上
...you can count the change in my pocket?
都能数清我口袋里的零钱了
Don't worry.
别担心
I imagine he'd be okay with you because he's okay with Ethan.
我猜他不会介意 因为他都没介意我和伊森
Ethan? There's an Ethan?
伊森 还有个伊森
Ethan is my...
伊森是我的...
...boyfriend.
男朋友
What?
啥
So, uh, what kind of relationship do you imagine us having...
额 那咱俩目前这算是什么关系呢
...if you already have a husband and a boyfriend?
既然你已经有了丈夫和男朋友
I suppose, mainly sexual.
主要是..性关系吧
I'm sorry it didn't work out.
真替你感到遗憾
What not work out? I'm seeing her again on Thursday.
遗憾啥 我和她约了周四见啊
Didn't you listen to the story?
你没听明白刚才的故事吗
是你没明白吧
How could you get involved with a woman like this?
你怎么还能和这样的女人搞在一起
I had trouble with it at first, but I get all the good stuff.
我开始也很纠结 不过后来我看开了
All the fun, all the talking, all the sex...
和她约会既有趣 有的聊 还能上床
...and no responsibility.
而且还没责任
This is every guy's fantasy!
这是每个男人的梦想啊
That is not true. Ross, is this your fantasy?
扯呢吧 罗斯 这是你的梦想吗
No, of course not.
必须不是啊
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
没错 是我的梦想
You'd go out with someone else who's going out with someone else?
你们就不介意约会的女生有其他男人吗
I couldn't.
我忍不了
Good for you. Joey
就你还靠谱点 乔伊
When I'm with a woman, I need to know...
如果我和一个女的约会 我必须确定
...that I'm going out with more people than she is.
我的备胎比她更多
You know...
其实吧
...monogamy can be a tricky concept.
一夫一妻制是个挺复杂的概念
I mean, anthropologically...
从人类学的角度...
Fine. Now you'll never know.
好吧 你们失去了学习知识的机会
We're kidding. Tell us.
开玩笑呢 说吧
We wanna know.
我们都想知道
All right. There's a theory put forth by Richard Leakey...
好吧 理查德里奇有一个理论说...
Are we greeting each other this way now? I like that.
现在流行这么打招呼吗 我还挺喜欢的
Look! I cleaned!
快看 我打扫了房间
I did the windows. I did the floors.
擦了窗户 擦了地板
I used all the attachments on the vacuum except for that round one.
吸尘器上的所有部件我都用了 除了一个圆形的
I don't know what it's for.
我不知道是干啥用的
Nobody knows, and we're not supposed to ask.
没人知道 而且没人敢问
What do you think?
你们觉得咋样
-It's very clean.  -Really, it looks great!
-挺干净的  -相当不错
Oh. Heh. I see you moved the green ottoman.
噢 你把绿色软椅放到这了啊
How did that happen?
为啥放这儿
I don't know. I thought it looked better there.
我觉得放到那挺好看的啊
And also, it's an extra seat around the coffee table.
而且这样就多出来了一个座位
Yeah, it's interesting.
挺有新意
But you know what? Just for fun...
不过...我纯属娱乐啊
...let's see what it looked like in the old spot.
咱们看看以前的摆法怎么样
Just to compare.
比较一下
Let's see. Ha!
我看看啊
Well, it looks good there too.
放在这也挺好看的
Let's leave it there for a while.
那就在这放一阵吧
I can't believe you tried to move the green ottoman.
你居然敢移动那个软椅
Thank God you didn't fan out the magazines.
还好你没摊开那些杂志
She'll scratch your eyes out.
要不她得把你眼睛挖出来
You guys, I am not that bad!
嘿 我没那么偏执吧
Yeah, you are. Monica
没错 你就是
Remember, I lived with you?
还记得我住这里的时候吗
You were a little, you know...
你就像这样...
That is so unfair!
太扯了吧
When we were kids, yours was the only Raggedy Ann doll that wasn't raggedy.
咱们小的时候 只有你的破烂娃娃是不破的
Okay, so I'm responsible. I'm organized.
好吧 我负责任 有条理
But, hey, I can be a kook!
我也可以很邋遢啊
All right, you madcap gal!
好吧 狂野美少女
Try to imagine this.
试想一下这个
The phone bill arrives, but you don't pay it right away.
电话单到了 但是你却没有马上去交费
-Why not? -Because you're a kook!
-为啥  -因为你邋遢啊
Instead, you wait until they send you a notice.
而且你一直拖到他们提醒你
I could do that.
没问题
Okay, then you let me go grocery shopping...
试试这个 你让我去杂货店买东西
...and I buy laundry detergent.
我买了洗衣液
But it's not the one with the easy-pour spout.
但不是那种有简易倒口的款
Why would someone do that?
为啥啊
One might wonder.
我替别人问的
A glass is on the table. There's no coaster.
一杯水在桌子上 没有杯垫
It's a cold drink. It's a hot day.
一杯凉水 天气又很热
Beads of condensation are inching their way closer to the wood...
杯子上的小水珠逐渐逼近干净的桌面
Stop it!
别说了
Oh, my God!
我的天
It's true. Who am I?
还真是 我是谁啊
Monica, you're Mom.
莫妮卡 你和咱妈一样
Uh-huh? Oh, my God!
好啊 我天
Okay.
没问题
Okay, I'll be there.
我一定准时到场
That was my agent.
我经纪人打来的
My agent has just gotten me a job in the new Al Pacino movie!
她刚给我争取到了一个角色 在艾尔·帕西诺的新电影里
(艾尔·帕西诺: '教父', '闻香识女人')
Whoa! That's great!
太棒了吧
What's the part?
演的什么角色
Can you believe this? Al Pacino!
难以置信 艾尔·帕西诺啊
This guy's why I became an actor.
因为他我才当的演员
"I'm out of order? You're out of order!
'我失控 你们才失控了吧
(电影'伸张正义'台词)
This whole courtroom's out of order!"
整个法庭都失控了'
(电影'伸张正义'台词)
Seriously, what's the part?
什么角色啊
"Just when I thought I was out, they pull me back in!"
'正当我想退出的时候 他们就把我拉回来'
(电影'教父3'台词)
Come on. Seriously, Joey, what's the part?
行了 乔伊 到底是什么角色啊
You're, you're... What?
你演...说啥呢
I'm his butt double, okay?
我演他屁股的替身
I play Al Pacino's butt.
演的是帕西诺的屁股
All right? He goes into the shower, and then...
就这样 他进屋洗澡 然后...
...I'm his butt.
我演他的屁股
Oh, my God!
我晕
Come on, you guys.
拜托 别这样吧
This is a real movie, and Al Pacino's in it and that's big!
这是个正经电影啊 艾尔·帕西诺主演的大制作
Oh, no, it's terrific.
对 棒极了
After all your years of struggling...
你在影坛挣扎了这么多年
...you've finally been able to crack your way into show business.
终于拱开了一条路啊
Okay, fine. Make jokes, I don't care.
尽情嘲笑我吧 我不在乎
This is a big break for me!
这对我来说是个突破
You're right. It is.
没错 确实是
So are you gonna invite us all to the big opening?
那邀请我们去看首映式吗
-I need to borrow some moisturizer. -For what?
-我要借点保湿霜  -干啥用啊
What do you think? Today's the big day!
还能干啥 今天就要上镜头了
Okay, go into the bathroom. Use whatever you want.
好吧 在厕所里呢 想用啥用啥
Just don't ever tell me what you did in there.
只是别告诉我你干啥了
Thank you.
谢啦
-Joey's mom's on the phone. -He's in the bathroom.
-乔伊呢 她妈找他  -厕所
-You don't wanna go in there! -Come on, we're roommates.
-我劝你别进去  -没事 都是室友
My eyes! My eyes!
亮瞎我的狗眼啊
I warned you.
警告过你了
Who is being loud?
谁瞎叫唤呢啊
Oh, that would be Monica.
莫妮卡喊的
Can I borrow some things? I wanna make Aurora breakfast.
能借点东西么 我想给奥萝拉做点吃的
You got the whole night, huh?
约了一整晚啊 小伙
Well, I only have 20 minutes until Ethan, so...
再过20分钟以后就轮到伊森了 你懂的
Do I sense a bit of resentment?
我好像感受到了一点恨意啊
No, no, no. No resentment. Believe me...
没有 绝对没有恨意 相信我
...it's worth it, okay?
超值的
In a relationship, you have these key moments...
你知道在恋爱里会有许多
...you'll remember for the rest of your life.
值得记一辈子的瞬间吧
Well, every single second is like that with Aurora.
和奥萝拉每一秒都值得铭记
And I've just wasted 35 of them talking to you.
而我刚浪费了35秒和你们扯淡
So, uh, Monica, can you help me with the door?
莫妮卡 帮我开下门吧
Um, Chandler, you know, the old Monica would remind you...
钱德 以前的莫妮卡会提醒你
...to scrub that Teflon pan with a plastic brush.
用塑胶刷擦这个盘子
But I'm not gonna do that.
但是我不会
Damn it! Hire the girl.
见鬼 雇用那个女的
Okay, everybody ready?
都准备好了吗
Uh, listen, I just wanna thank you for this great opportunity.
拍之前 我想感谢您能给我这次机会
Lose the robe.
把浴袍脱了
Me?
我吗
That would work.
没错
Right. Okay. Losing the robe!
没问题 马上脱
Okay, and the robe is lost.
脱浴袍完毕
Everybody, I would like to get this in one take.
好了 尽量一遍就过啊
Let's roll it.
准备
Water's working.
放水
And action!
开拍
And cut!
卡
Butt guy, what are you doing?
屁股男 你干啥呢
I'm showering.
洗澡啊
No, that was clenching.
不对 你在挤屁股
Well, the way I see it, the guy's upset here, you know?
对 据我观察 主人公现在应该很郁闷
His wife's dead, his brother's missing.
媳妇死了 兄弟失踪了
I think his butt would be angry here.
我想他的屁股应该挺生气的
I think his butt would like to get the shot before lunch.
我认为他的屁股想在午饭前杀青
Once again, rolling. Water working.
再来一次 准备 放水
And action!
开拍
And cut! What was that?
卡 又搞毛呢
I was going for quiet desperation.
我想表现出一种绝望
But if you have to ask...
如果你非要问的话
God, I love these fingers.
我爱死这双手了
Thank you.
谢谢
No, actually, I meant my fingers.
我说的是我的手
Look at them. Look at how happy they are.
看它们多开心啊
-Oh, my God, I'm late! -Oh, no, no, no.
-噢 我要迟到了 -没有 没有
-Don't go, don't go. -Okay, okay.
-别走 别离开  -好吧
-I have to. -Look, she's leaving.
-我得走了  -她走了
I'm sorry. He'll be waiting for me.
抱歉 他在等着我呢
I thought you talked to Rick.
我以为你和瑞克说过了
It's not Rick.
不是瑞克
Ethan? He gets the whole day with you!
伊森已经占了你一天啊
No, it's Andrew.
不是 是安德鲁
I know there'll be many moments...
我知道以后我肯定会
...when I'll regret asking the following question, but...
经常后悔我问了这个问题 但是...
And Andrew is?
安德鲁是谁啊
He's... new.
他是 新欢
So you're not completely fulfilled by Rick, Ethan and myself?
所以瑞克 伊森再加上我 都不能满足你吗
No, that's not exactly what I was...
不是 我并没有这么觉得...
Most women would kill...
无数女同胞都会被
...for three guys like us.
我们三个秒杀啊
So, what do you want?
那你想要怎么样
You.
你
-You have me. -No, no. Just you.
-你有我啊  -不是 只有你
What do you mean?
什么意思
Lose the other guys.
把其他人都甩了吧
Like, all of them?
全都甩了吗
Come on, we're great together. Why not?
是啊 我们在一起很棒 不行吗
Why can't we just have what we have now?
为什么不能维持现状呢
Why can't we just talk, laugh and make love...
只是聊天 大笑 做爱...
...without feeling obligated to one another?
而丝毫不用担心被绑住
Up until tonight, I thought that's what you wanted too.
今晚之前我以为你也是这么想的
Well, part of me wants that...
一部分的我想要这样
...but it's like I'm two guys.
但是我身体里有两个小人
I mean, one guy's saying, "Shut up! This is great!"
一个说'闭嘴 这样多好啊'
But there's this other guy.
但是另外一个
It's the guy who wells up every time the Grinch's heart...
他每次都会跳出来
...grows three sizes and breaks that measuring device.
阻止我越陷越深
He's saying, you know, "This is too hard. Get out, get out!"
他一直说'这太扭曲了 快离开她'
So which one of the two guys will you listen to?
那你会听谁的建议呢
I have to listen to both. They don't let each other finish.
都听 因为他们总是不让对方说完
Which one?
哪一个
The second guy.
第二个
I see.
懂了
Call me if you change your mind.
改变主意了就打电话给我
Sorry, the first guy runs the lips.
抱歉 第一个小人动的嘴
Look at it this way. You dumped her!
换个角度看 是你甩的她
Right? I mean, this woman was...
对吧 这个女的长得
...unbelievably sexy...
异常的火辣
...and beautiful, intelligent, unattainable...
美丽 聪明 可望而不可即
Tell me why you did this again?
告诉我你为啥分手来着
Movie star!
大明星来啦
Aren't you the guy who plays the butt in the new Al Pacino movie?
你不是演艾尔·帕西诺屁股的影星嘛
Nope.
不是
No? What happened, big guy?
不是吗 发生什么了 猛男
Big guy?
猛男
It felt like a "big guy" moment.
我觉得这应该是个'猛男时刻'
I got fired!
我被炒了
They said I acted too much with it.
他们说我的表演太过了
I told everybody about this.
所有人都知道我要演出
Everybody will be expecting to see me.
他们还都等着看我呢
You know what? No one will be able to tell.
别担心 反正他们也认不出来
My mom will.
我妈妈能啊
There's something so sweet...
真是令人既感动
...and disturbing about that.
又反胃啊
I've done nothing but crappy plays for six years...
我这六年除了演烂片没干别的
...and I finally get my shot, and I blow it!
终于有个机会翻身 我却搞砸了
Maybe this wasn't your shot.
也许这并不是真正的机会
I think when it's your shot, you know it's your shot.
没错 当机会来临的时候 你会清晰的感觉到
Did it feel like your shot?
你有这种感觉吗
Hard to tell. I was naked.
难说 毕竟是裸体拍的
I don't think this was your shot.
我认为这不是你的机会
I don't even think you just get one shot.
我觉得你翻身的机会还没来
I really believe big things are gonna happen for you. I do.
但是我相信你以后会飞黄腾达 一定会
You've gotta keep thinking about the day that some kid will go...
总有一天会有一个小孩子大喊
..."I got the part! I'm gonna be Joey Tribbiani's ass!"
'我拿到这个角色了 演乔伊·崔比昂尼的屁股'
You think? That's so nice.
真的吗 你太好了
Oh, come here.
走一个吧
I'm sorry, Joey. I'm gonna go to bed, guys.
开心点 乔伊 我去睡觉了
Good night.
晚安
You're gonna leave your shoes out here?
你打算把鞋留在那吗
Really? Just casually strewn about...
真的吗 就这么随手一扔
...in that reckless, haphazard manner?
简单随意的撇在那边
It doesn't matter. I'll get them tomorrow. Or not!
没关系 明天再说吧 没准就一直放那了
Whenever.
不在意
She is a kook.
她还真能邋遢啊
If it bothers you that much, just go out and get the shoes.
如果这么在意 出去把鞋捡起来啊
No, don't do this!
别 千万别捡
This is stupid!
这太二了
I don't have to prove anything. I'm gonna go get them.
我又不用证明什么 我要去捡起来
But then everyone will know.
可是这样所有人就会知道了
Unless I get them, and then wake up really early and put them back.
除非我捡起来 然后明天早起再放回去
I need help!
谁来帮帮我啊